Let's talk about the
doom loop What's your
theory First I have
to share with you
more of the macroeconomic
moment that Southeast Asia
is in And this
one is like I
didn't make this up
11 years ago I
watched a on YouTube
and I felt that
it so succinct the
way it described how
I felt the working
And Ray Dalio of
does a good job
at all of this
right His video is
called How the Economic
Machine Works So I'm
definitely butchering Ray I'm
try to something that
I watched 11 years
ago right But roughly
speaking I think people
can relate to it
is that you have
the of as
a business of
like earning money right
And as a are
good to lend you
money because you actually
have actual earnings and
profits to be able
to lend against And
because you get the
lend money
you borrow this money
right You borrow this
money from and then
you that money on
productive things like machinery
or like people and
whatnot right And because
of that like you
start earning more
I believe you had
one more thing but
I'm just gonna simplify
it right So then
you get to earn
more Now the thing
is that when you
get to more money
then you get to
more money then you
get to more money
and then you get
to more money And
this kind of like
multiplies across like and
millions of businesses and
then it keeps going
up and up and
up And then that's
how the macro increases